<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Delhi</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="indiagate">India Gate</string>
    <string name="coronation">Coronation Durbar Park</string>
    <string name="redfort">Red Fort</string>
    <string name="qutubminar">Qutub Minar</string>
    <string name="humayuntomb">Humayun\'s Tomb</string>
    <string name="lodhigarden">Lodhi Garden</string>
    <string name="safdarjung">Safdarjung\'s Tomb</string>
    <string name="jamamasjid">Jama Masjid</string>
    <string name="parliament">Parliament House</string>
    <string name="rajghat">Raj Ghat</string>
    <string name="shantivan">Shantivan</string>
    <string name="jantarmantar">Jantar Mantar</string>
    <string name="oldfort">Old Fort (Purana Qila)</string>
    <string name="indiagateDescription">The India Gate, (originally called the All India War Memorial), is a war memorial located astride the Rajpath, on the eastern edge of the ‘ceremonial axis’ of New Delhi, India, formerly called Kingsway. India Gate is a memorial to 82,000 soldiers of the undivided Indian Army who died in the period 1914–21 in the First World War, in France, Flanders, Mesopotamia, Persia, East Africa, Gallipoli and elsewhere in the Near and the Far East, and the Third Anglo-Afghan War. 13,516 servicemen\'s names, including some soldiers and officers from the United Kingdom, are inscribed on the gate. The India Gate, even though a war memorial, evokes the architectural style of the triumphal arch like the Arch of Constantine, outside the Colosseum in Rome, and is often compared to the Arc de Triomphe in Paris, and the Gateway of India in Mumbai. It was designed by Sir Edwin Lutyens.
        \n\nIn 1971, following the Bangladesh Liberation war, a small simple structure, consisting of a black marble plinth, with reversed rifle, capped by war helmet, bounded by four eternal flames, was built beneath the soaring Memorial Archway. This structure, called Amar Jawan Jyoti, or the Flame of the Immortal Soldier, since 1971 has served as India\'s Tomb of the Unknown Soldier.
    </string>
    <string name="coronationDescription">The Coronation Durbar Park, also known as the Coronation Memorial was the venue of the Delhi Durbar in 1877 after Queen Victoria was declared the Empress of India. In 1903 the park was later used to celebrate King Edward’s assumption of the throne in 1903.
        \n\nIt was at the same place that the coronation of King George the fifth as Emperor of India took place as well in December 1911. The park is also home to the tallest statue of King George the Fifth which used to be under the Canopy near India Gate and was later removed from there in the 1960’s and placed here.
        \n\nThe park which was initially in a state of neglect has been restored by the Indian National Trust for Art and Cultural Heritage and the Government of Delhi.
    </string>
    <string name="redfortDescription">The Red Fort-a massive red sandstone fort is synonymous with Delhi and is proof of the glory of the flourishing Mughal Empire in Delhi.
        \n\nCommissioned by Shah Jahan in 1638 when he decided to shift the capital of the Mughal Empire from Agra to Delhi, the Red Fort took a total of ten years to be completed. The main gate to the Red Fort is the Lahore Gate and is also the site for the Prime Ministers speech every year on Independence Day. A UNESCO World Heritage Site, the Red Fort is spread over a rambling 254.67 acres and the walls alone are around 2kilometres long.
        \n\nThe Red Fort is octagonal in design and there are beautiful flower decorations and calligraphy on the walls, examples of later Mughal style architecture. At one point the Read Fort was surrounded by a deep moat, used to keep intruders out. The Red Fort contains the Diwan-e-Aam, the Diwan-e-Khas, the Moti Masjid and the Hayat Baksh Bagh among other interesting architectural elements.
    </string>
    <string name="qutubminarDescription">The Qutub Minar is a towering 73 meter high tower built by Qutub-ud-Din Aibak in 1193. The tower was built to celebrate Muslim dominance in Delhi after the defeat of Delhi’s last Hindu ruler. This tower is the highest tower in India, complete with five storeys and projecting balconies. The first three storeys of the Qutub Minar are made of red sandstone and the last two are made of marble and sandstone.
        \n\nThe construction of the Qutub Minar was started by Qitub-ud-Din Aibak, but he only constructed the basement. The construction of the tower was later taken over by his successor Iltutmish who constructed three more stories. The last two storeys were completed Firoz Shah Tuglak. The different architectural styles from the time of Aibak to Tuglak are clearly visible in the Qutub Minar.
        \n\nApart from the tower, the Qutub Minar complex comprises of the Quwwat-us-Islam Mosque (the first mosque to be built in India), a 7 metre high iron pillar, the tomb of Iltutmish, Ala’i-Darwaza and the Ala’I Minar.
    </string>
    <string name="humayuntombDescription">One of the most magnificent tombs built in Delhi during the Mughal rule, the Humayun’s Tomb is an excellent example of Persian architecture. The Humayun’s Tomb was commissioned in 1526, nine years after the death of Humayun, by his widow Hamida Banu Begum.
        \n\nConstructed out of red sandstone, the Humayun’s Tomb was the first ever garden style tomb to be constructed in India. The Humayun’s Tomb stands in the centre of Charbagh style of gardens complete with pools linked by channels. The main entrance if the tomb is from the south side, though there is another entrance from the west side as well.
        \n\nThe Humayun’s Tomb served as an early example for other Mughal tombs which were built over time, such as the Akbar’s tomb in Sikander, the tomb of Ghiyas-ud-Din Tugluq at Tugluqabad, the tomb of Sikander Lodi in the Lodi Gardens and the Taj Mahal.
        \n\nIn the Humayun’s Tomb one can see architectural features which over time went on to become important component of Mughal architecture, such as its octagonal shape and its high central arch.
        \n\nApart from Humayun, the tomb is also the final resting place of his wife Hamida Bahu Begum, Shah Jahan’s son Dara Shikoh and other prominent Mughals from the royal family. A UNESCO World Heritage Site, the Humayun’s tomb is best visited in the late afternoon if you wish to get some beautiful shots of the building.
    </string>
    <string name="lodhigardenDescription">Dotted with monuments and tombs from the Lodi and Sayyed periods of history, the Lodi Gardens in one of Delhi’s popular tourist attractions. Emblematic of 16th century architectural styles, the Lodi Gardens contain the tombs of Muhammad Shah and Sikandar Lodi. 
        \n\nDespite being a historical monument, the Lodi Gardens has become an integral part of the lives of many Delhites as many picnickers, walkers and joggers frequent the gardens in the mornings and evenings.
        \n\nThe Lodi Gardens also contain the National Bonsai Park, which is home to a wide variety miniature tress. The best time to go to the Lodi Gardens is around sunset when the sunlight is mellow and the tombs are beautifully lit up."
    </string>
    <string name="safdarjungDescription">The last garden tomb in Delhi, the Safdarjung’s Tomb is the mausoleum of Safdarjung. Built between 1753-54 by Safdarjung’s son Shuja-ud-Daula this tomb has numerous small canopies, such as the Moti Mahal, Badsha Pasand and Jangli Mahal among others. The complex of the Hunayun’s Tomb also contains a Madrasa and a library maintained by the archeological survey of India.
        \n\nConstructed in the centre of the Charbagh style gardens, a popular architectural style in Mughal constructions, Safdarjung’s Tomb is decorated with ponds and fountains. Crafted out of red sandstone with a white marble dome, the Safdarjung’s Tomb is built on a raised platform with a gate to its east and spacious walkways on the other three sides.
    </string>
    <string name="jamamasjidDescrition">Shah Jahan’s last architectural extravagance, the Jama Masjid towers over Old Delhi and is India’s largest mosque. Commissioned by Shah Jahan in 1650 the mosque took six years to be constructed and was completed in 1656. The massive courtyard of the Jama Masjid can hold up to twenty five thousand worshippers and houses many interesting relics, including an ancient copy of the Quran inscribed on deer skin.
        \n\nThe main prayer hall of the Jama Masjid is topped with three white bulbous domes and the entrance is adorned with high rising arches which cover the mihrab (an alcove in the wall which indicates the direction of prayer). A pool in the centre of the mosque is used by the faithful for ablutions before prayer.
        \n\nThe Jama Masjid is flanked by slim red and white minarets on all four sides which reach high into the sky. In the north east corner of the mosque is a small shrine which houses relics of Prophet Muhammad, such as a red hair from his beard, his sandals and his footprint imprinted on a marble slab.
    </string>
    <string name="parliamenthouseDescription">Parliament House or Sansad Bhavan is one of the most impressive buildings in Delhi. Located at the end of Sansad Marg the Parliament Building was designed by British architect Edwin Lutyens and Herbert Baker. This iconic building was inaugurated in 1972 by Lord Irwin, the then Governor-General of India.
        \n\nThe Parliament House comprises of a central hall which is circular in shape and 98 feet in diameter. The Central Hall is considered to be a very important part of the Parliament building since this is where the Indian Constitution was drafted. The building houses the Lok Sabha, Rajya Sabha and a library hall. In between these three chambers lies a garden. The building also has facilities for accommodation for ministers, important officers of the Lok Sabha and Rajya Sabha, Chairmen and Parliamentary Committees.
        \n\nThe Parliament House also houses a museum which aims at educating people on the “Democratic Heritage of India” and which dates back to 2500 back. The museum is set up in a very interesting way and is complete with sound and light videos, large screen interactive computer screens and virtual reality among other features.
    </string>
    <string name="rajghatDescrition">Raj Ghat is the memorial of Mahatma Gandhi, the Father of the Nation. A black stone platform in an open air complex marks the spot where Gandhi was cremated. A flame constantly burns at one end of the platform and visitors are required to remove their footwear before they enter Raj Ghat. Also close to the Raj Ghat is the memorial of Jawaharlal Nehru, known as Shantivan.</string>
    <string name="shantivanDescription">Shantivan, or the Forest of Peace, is the Samadhi, or cremation spot of India’s first Prime Minister, Jawaharlal Nehru. The samadi in the form of a large base covered with a lawn is located north of Raj Ghat, the Samadhi of Mahatma Gandhi. Shantivan is visited by many visiting dignitaries and heads of state who come here to pay their respects. Special prayer services are organised on the birth and death anniversaries of Nehru. Cultural programs by children also take place, since Nehru loved children and they in turn fondly called him Chacha Nehru.</string>
    <string name="jantarmantarDescrition">Jantar Mantar is an observatory constructed by Maharaja Jai Singh of Jaipur in 1724. The essential purpose of the Jantar Mantar was to accumulate astronomical tables which in turn would help predict the time and movement of the celestial bodies such as the sun, moon and other planets.
        \n\nThe Jantar Mantar comprises of various instruments which helped with these predictions, such as the Samrat Yantra, Jayaprakash Yantra and the Misra Yantra among others. After constructing the Jantar Mantar in Delhi, Raja Jai Singh constructed more such structures by the same name in Jaipur, Ujjain, Mathura and Varanasi. The Jantar Mantar remains a popular tourist destination and is a great place for lovers of astronomy.
    </string>
    <string name="oldfortDescription">One of the oldest forts in India, the Pura Qila was constructed by the Afghan King, Sher Shah Suri on what was supposed to be Indraprastha, the capital of the Pandavas. The walls of the Old Fort rise to a height of 18 metres and are spread over 1.5 kilometres. The fort has three main entrances, the Bada Darwaza which faces west and is used as the entrance to the fort even today. The South Gate is known as the Humayun Gate and the third gate is called the Talaqi Gate or the forbidden gate.
        \n\nAll three gates are double storey structures constructed using sandstone and are surrounded by two large semicircular towers adorned with coloured marble embellishments and blue tile work. At the North and South Gates of the Purana Qila you will find beautiful balconies, chattris and pavilions which only add to the grandeur of the fort.
    </string>
    <string name="monuments">Monuments</string>
    <string name="map">Map</string>
    <string name="museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="air_force_museum">Air Force Museum</string>
    <string name="archeologic_museum">Archaeological Museum</string>
    <string name="crafts_museum">Craft Museum</string>
    <string name="national_police_museum">National Police Museum</string>
    <string name="science_center">National Science Center</string>
    <string name="rail_museum">National Rail Museum</string>
    <string name="nehru_museum">Nehru Museum and Planetarium</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail">DetailActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="air_forceDescription">A collection of aeroplanes &amp; armoury depicts the history of the Indian Air force &amp; has a vast collection of aeroplanes and armoury on display.</string>
    <string name="archeologyDescription">Paintings, Textiles Costumes. Situated in the historic Red Fort, the museum exhibits objects that date to the mughal period. One section concentrates on the relics of the 1857 war (First War of Independence) like maps and weapons.</string>
    <string name="craftsDescription">Indian crafts, Wooden Carvings, Metal ware, Paintings. Mud huts with Painted walls and Thatched roofs, Courtyards, Terracotta horses recreating Village shrines, Craftsmen at work are some of the elements that add to the rural ambience of the place.</string>
    <string name="policeDescription">"The world of thrill and sensation.
        \n\nThis museum takes us into the world of thrill and sensation as museum contains several thought provoking items all related to police, Crime &amp; Criminals, from the ancient to the modern times. Exhibited items are acquired from different states and central police organizations both of Indian and Foreign Origin. Photography is allowed with permission. Museum has no admission fees."</string>
    <string name="science_centerDescription">Constructed in 8 floors, this museum houses working science exhibition as well as exhibits on the history of architecture. It has various sections for all age groups such as Heritage &amp; Dinosaur gallery, Human Biology gallery, Fun Science Library etc. There are also a number of hands-on displays explaining the laws of physics. The Cyberlkool of this museum is the first fun-packed multimedia centre in the country. At least a whole day is required to go through this "children\'s" paradise.</string>
    <string name="railDescription">"This unique museum has a fascinating and exotic collection of over 100 real size exhibits of Indian Railways. Static and working models, signaling equipments, antique furnitures, historical photographs and related literature etc. are displayed in the museum. The line-up of old coaches includes the handsome Prince of Wales Saloon, built in 1875. Not to be outdone is the Maharaja of Mysore\'s Saloon built in 1899 with its brocade covered chairs and an elegant rosewood bed; one can peer in through the windows for a good look. National Rail Museum, the star attraction here is the Fairy Queen, built in 1855 and considered to be one of the best preserved steam locomotive engines of her age. A ride in joy train and mono rail (PSMT) is the most exciting experience besides boating. Do not miss the handsome Fire Engine on your way out."</string>
    <string name="nehru_museumDescription">"Newspaper Clippings And Photographs From The Independence Movement.
        \n\nThe residence of Late Jawaharlal Nehru, the first Prime Minister of India was converted into a museum after his death. The museum is a fascinating place to learn about the history of the Independence Movement.
        \n\nThere are several photographs of the erstwhile Prime Minister, giving an account of his life. Besides this, the colonial building is also equally interesting, with its teak paneled rooms with high ceilings, spacious verandas and well kept gardens."</string>
    <string name="directions">directions</string>
    <string name="locIndiaGate">India+Gate</string>
    <string name="locCoronation">Coronation+Durbar+Park</string>
    <string name="locRedFort">Red+Fort</string>
    <string name="locQutubMinar">Qutub+Minar</string>
    <string name="locHumayunTomb">Humayun+Tomb</string>
    <string name="locLodhiGarden">Lodhi+Garden</string>
    <string name="locSafdarjung">Safdarjung+Tomb</string>
    <string name="locJamaMasjid">Jama+Masjid</string>
    <string name="locParliament">Paarliament+House</string>
    <string name="locRajGhat">Raj+Ghat</string>
    <string name="locShantivan">Shantivan</string>
    <string name="locJantarMantar">Jantar+Mantar</string>
    <string name="locOldFort">Old+Fort</string>
    <string name="locAirForce">Air+Force+Museum</string>
    <string name="locArchaeological">Archaeological+Museum+Red+Fort</string>
    <string name="locCrafts">Crafts+Museum</string>
    <string name="locPolice">National+Police+Museum</string>
    <string name="locScience">National+Science+Center</string>
    <string name="locRail">National+Rail+Museum</string>
    <string name="locNehru">Nehru+Planetarium</string>
    <string name="delhi_public_library">Delhi Public Library</string>
    <string name="american_library">The American Library</string>
    <string name="british_library">British Council Library India</string>
    <string name="habitat_library">India Habitat Centre – Habitat Library and Resource Centre</string>
    <string name="japan_library">The Japan Foundation Library</string>
    <string name="nehru_library">Nehru Memorial Library {Teen Murti Library}</string>
    <string name="sahitya_library">Sahitya Kala Akademi Library</string>
    <string name="delhi_libraryDescription">All you have to do is carry proof of residency {voter ID, Ration card}, to show you’re a Delhi resident. The library is free of charge, and houses up to 16 lakh books, across languages, including English, Hindi, Urdu and Sanskrit. As for genres, expect competitive examination books, books pertaining to law, philosophy, religion, medical science, engineering, literature, and fiction. We hear they have a stellar collection of books authored by early Indian writers, and that too, in excellent shape. If you do want to borrow, you’ll have to sign up to be a member at INR 20, after which you’ll be issued a borrower card.</string>
    <string name="americanDescription">General public has free access to the library, in case you’re just looking for some quiet down time. But, a membership will entitle you to borrow up to four books, two back issues of periodicals and two DVD’s. A member is also allowed access to library accounts online, to create search lists, renew material and place hold requests for material available. Membership is open to anyone over the age of 16, and you will require proper photo identification. As for borrowing, you can ask for loans online, in person and even request an inter library loan, from libraries in different states. Also-free Wi-Fi within the library!</string>
    <string name="britishDescription">Any UK return student will know the drill all too well. The British Council Library requires you to enroll as a member, which will entitle you to more than 85,000 online academic books and 14,000 e-journals online. Moreover, membership ensures you’re invited to workshops, seminars, and events. They have a plethora of membership plans, that differ in terms of validity, fees, borrowing rules and access.</string>
    <string name="habitatDescription">The Habitat library is open only to members, and the staff isn’t very well equipped to guide you or provide any real, useful information. The library itself offers a range of resources, including newspapers, electronic newspapers, internet, multimedia, videos, music and books. The books aren’t exhaustive; look at this as a quiet place to be able to get some work done.</string>
    <string name="japanDescription">If you’re a manga fan, you’ve just found a fan club. This particular library is country specific, and provides reference services for the collection, and research info related to Japan, and international cultural exchange. You are entitled to borrow, use available multimedia tools, and photocopy. Membership is open to all, provided you’re a Delhi/NCR resident. In case you only want to use the library for a day or two, ask for a daily membership card.</string>
    <string name="nehru_libraryDescription">At their nominal membership fee, don’t expect some grade A service or information. Relatively well-stocked, they’re open seven days a week and will definitely deliver, if you’re looking for an old school library and some down time. Lending is allowed, and a fine is charged if and when you lose the book. Membership will involve you physically visiting and having a card issued. Old school. We told you.</string>
    <string name="sahityaDescription">One of the most important and well-stocked libraries in the city is the Akademi Library. It has books in Hindi, English and 24 other languages that students, researchers and almost anyone can come and refer to. Apart from issuing books, they also have a photocopying and scanning facility, in case you need hard or soft copies of any information. They mainly focus on cultural and historical books that are related to the cultural and social history of the country. We hope you visit and take advantage of the privilege.</string>
    <string name="locDelLibrary">Delhi+Public+Library</string>
    <string name="locAmericanLibrary">The+American+Library</string>
    <string name="locBritishLibrary">British+Council+Library+India</string>
    <string name="locHabitatLibrary">India+Habitat+Center</string>
    <string name="locJapanLibrary">The+Japan+Foundation+Library</string>
    <string name="locNehruLibrary">Nehru+Memorial+Library</string>
    <string name="locSahityaLibrary">Sahitya+Kala+Akademi+Library</string>
    <string name="libraries">Libraries</string>
    <string name="parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="buddhaJayantiPark">Buddha Jayanti Park</string>
    <string name="locBuddha">Buddha+Jayanti+Park</string>
    <string name="buddhaDescription">The Buddha Jayanti Smarak Park is situated in southern part of the Delhi ridge in New Delhi, India.
        \n\nIt was created on the occasion of the 2500th anniversary of Gautama Buddha\'s enlightenment. A sapling of the Bodhi Tree from Sri Lanka was planted here by the then Prime Minister of India Shri. Lal Bahadur Shastri on 25 October 1964
        \n\nOn an artificial island in the park stands pavilion with a gilded Buddha statue in it. It was dedicated by the 14th Dalai Lama in October 1993.
        \n\nEach year in May on Vaisakha Full moon day the Buddha Jayanti festival is celebrated here.</string>
    <string name="deerPark">Deer Park</string>
    <string name="locDeerPark">Deer+Park</string>
    <string name="deerParkDescription">Deer Park is located in South Delhi also known as A.N. Jha Deer Park, named after famous Social worker Aditya Nath Jha. This place is popular for walking, jogging and weekend outings. The Deer Park comprises many subsection such as Duck Park, Picnic Spots Rabbit Enclosures etc. The Park has historical tombs of Mughal Era. The park is accessible from Safdarjung Enclave and Green Park, Hauz Khas Village. It is also connected to District Park thus making is approachable from R K Puram near the courts side of the Delhi Lawn Tennis Association.</string>
    <string name="gardenOf5Senses">Garden of Five Senses</string>
    <string name="locGardenof5Senses">Garden+of+5+Senses</string>
    <string name="gardenDescription">The Garden of Five Senses is a park spread over 20 acres, in Saidul Ajaib village, opposite Saket, near the Mehrauli heritage area in Delhi, India. Designed by Delhi architect, Pradeep Sachdeva, the park was developed by Delhi Tourism and Transportation Development Corporation, Delhi at a cost of Rs 10.5 crore (105,000,000 rupees), over a period of three years and opened in February 2003. Partly built over a rocky terrain, the garden has various theme areas, including a section on the lines of Mughal Gardens, plus pools of water lilies, bamboo courts, herb gardens and solar energy park.</string>
    <string name="indraprasthaPark">Indraprastha Park</string>
    <string name="locIndraprastha">Indraprastha+Park</string>
    <string name="indraprasthaDecription">The Millennium Indraprastha Park is a park on the Outer Ring Road in the east of Delhi, India. It was constructed in 2004 by the Delhi Development Authority. The park includes a children\'s park, an amphitheatre and a food court.
        \n\nA large World Peace Stupa was opened in the park on 14th. November 2007 by monks and nuns of Nipponzan Myohoji, the 14th Dalai Lama, and the Lt. Governor of Delhi. This park was completely made from a landfill site.</string>
    <string name="nehruPark">Nehru Park</string>
    <string name="locNehruPark">Nehru+Park</string>
    <string name="nehruParkDescription">Nehru Park, Delhi, is a large park situated in the Chanakyapuri Diplomatic Enclave of New Delhi. Named after India\'s first Prime Minister, Jawaharlal Nehru, the park is spread over an area of 80 acres (320,000 m2), close to the heart of the city, and was established in 1969.
        \n\nIt is today one of city leading green areas, and a venue for \'Morning Ragas and Evening Ragas Concerts, as part of the "Music in the Park" concerts organized by NDMC, New Delhi Municipal Council, SPIC MACAY music concerts and the annual \'Bhakti Festival\'. Apart from this it is a regular venue for art events, morning yoga classes, and houses an ancient Shiv Temple and cafe. The park is one of the most famous landmarks of Delhi and a beautiful place to hang out during a sunny winter afternoon in Delhi. An absolute must see for anyone visiting Delhi.
        \n\nThe Park has a life size alloy statue of Vladimir Lenin the leader of the Great October Socialist Revolution of Russia. The statue was installed on Ist November 1987 during the 70th anniversary of October Revolution. It was unveiled by then Soviet Premier Nikolai Ryzhkov, Indian Prime-minister Rajiv Gandhi and his wife Sonia Gandhi. Every year on 22 April members of Communist Party of India (Marxist) and other Left oriented Political parties visits the place to commemorate the Birth Anniversary of Lenin.</string>
</resources>
